<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Erasmus&#43; IES Jaroso</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Erasmus&#43; IES Jaroso</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Acta baremación alumnos y profesores solicitantes de estancias Erasmus&#43; Ka131 2024-2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/actabaremacion2024ka131/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/actabaremacion2024ka131/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sólo hay un alumno que haya solicitado participar en Erasmus+ ka131 este curso entonces queda seleccionado automáticamente.&#xA;Respecto a los profesores, había dos solicitudes para dos plazas, en vista a los méritos presentados según el baremos han sido seleccionados José Miguel Sanz Mira y Javier Guillén Benavente.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adama is already in Italy to begin his Erasmus experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/gm_2024_adama_llegado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/gm_2024_adama_llegado/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to share that Adama has arrived in Rome as an Erasmus+ Laboratory student. He will be undertaking internships at a food laboratory in Arezzo for three months. We hope you learn a lot and have an unforgettable experience in this beautiful city!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students from IES Jaroso Vocational Training School ready to start their Erasmus 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/alumnosgm-erasmus-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/alumnosgm-erasmus-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Four students from IES Jaroso, Adama, Sarafina, María José, and Francina, from Vocational Training cycles in Laboratory, Administrative Management, and Welding, have just left the final Erasmus+ meeting and are already prepared to embark on this exciting Erasmus adventure. Soon, a student from the Higher Degree in Web Application Development will also join them. We wish them the best in this unique experience!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2024/foto1-gm.jpg&#34;&gt;Alumnos Erasmus GM 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grading of students and teachers requesting Erasmus&#43; stays Ka131 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/actabaremacion2023ka131/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/actabaremacion2023ka131/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is only one student who has requested to participate in Erasmus+ ka131 this course so he/she is automatically selected.&#xA;Regarding the teachers, there were three applications for two places, in view of the merits presented according to the scales, Javier Guillén Benavente and Ana Vicente Belmonte were selected.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening of the call for mobility stays in the Erasmus KA131 project in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/aperturaconvocaka131-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/aperturaconvocaka131-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The IES Jaroso opens a call for mobility stays for teachers and students for the 2023-2024 academic year. Two stays are called for students and another two for teachers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The teaching staff of the Higher degree cycles and the 2nd year students of the Higher degree cycles who are interested in completing their FCT in the European Union in the period between March and June 2024, must request it between January 15 from 2024 at 9:00 a.m. to January 23, 2024 at 2:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening of the call for mobility stays in the Erasmus KA131 project in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/aperturaconvocaka131-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/aperturaconvocaka131-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The IES Jaroso opens a call for mobility stays for teachers and students for the 2024-2025 academic year. Two stays are called for students and another two for teachers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The teaching staff of the Higher degree cycles and the 2nd year students of the Higher degree cycles who are interested in completing their FCT in the European Union in the period between March and June 2025, must request it between November 25 from 2024 at 9:00 a.m. to December 9, 2024 at 2:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Erasmus KA131 project awarded for Higher Degrees in Vocational Training</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/concedidoka131-2023-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/concedidoka131-2023-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The IES Jaroso will once again participate in an Erasmus project for higher-level vocational training. We have been awarded a KA131 project for the period 2023-2025.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have four stays available for students and two training stays for teachers for this period.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So we begin our Erasmus adventure again, let&amp;rsquo;s go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2023/ka131.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jaroso KA131&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel to Germany to tutor a student on site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/tutorizandoalemania-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/tutorizandoalemania-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This academic year 2022-2023 we have had a student doing his internship in Dusseldorf, Germany. This week the professor of the Laboratory training cycle, Jaime Usano, traveled there to tutor our student Nitai on site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This contact of the teacher with the reception centers is essential to establish long-term collaboration ties, improve the stay and training of the students and, ultimately, promote the Erasmus project at IES Jaroso.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We love seeing students working in companies in this way, and tutors so happy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students of the higher level training cycle in Web Application Development, doing the FCT in Ireland</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/alumnos2dawireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/alumnos2dawireland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This 2022-2023 academic year we have had two applicants to carry out an Erasmus+ mobility in the KA103 project that ends this year. As we had two mobilities left and there were two suitable applicants, the mobilities were automatically assigned to them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To find the destination, we interviewed the students and saw a good place to work related to our cycle and the foreign language that the students mastered. Finally the chosen country was Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The application period for Erasmus&#43; KA103 faculty mobility is open</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/abiertoplazoprofka103/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/abiertoplazoprofka103/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Call is open to apply for two Erasmus+ mobilities with the aim of either learning new techniques and methodologies related to the corresponding Professional Family, or learning new techniques and methodologies for good management of IES Jaroso. This type of mobility is not to go with students, only the teacher would go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;application&#34;&gt;APPLICATION&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whoever is interested, must fill out the attached application and deliver it to the Erasmus Coordinator Lorena Núñez Álvarez.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The application period for Erasmus &#43; mobility KA121 is open</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/abiertoplazoka121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/abiertoplazoka121/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The deadline for applying for Erasmus + mobility grants for internships for students of Basic and Middle degree cycles is open (for the completion of the FCT).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 2nd year students of our Basic and Medium degree cycles who are interested in taking their FCT in the European Union in the period between March and June 2022, must apply between December 17, 2021 at 9:00 as of December 22, 2021 at 2:00 p.m. To do this, they must fill in:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk Erasmus KA121</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/charlaerasmuska121/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/charlaerasmuska121/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, December 16, 2021, at 18:00, second year students from Basic FP and Middle Cycles interested in participating in the Erasmus Project will be invited to a face-to-face talk at IES Jaroso (door 35, ask at the Concierge).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This talk will be aimed at those students who wish to do Workplace Training in the European Union. In the event that a student is a minor, they may attend accompanied by their legal guardians.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessment of Erasmus&#43; summer scholarship applications for higher technical cycles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/baremacionka103verano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/baremacionka103verano/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We publish the scale of the applications submitted for Erasmus+ mobility grants in the summer period. There are two requests from students of the upper cycle of Guide, Information and Tourist Assistance, and this is the final order according to the scale made according to the criteria established and published on this website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening of the call for Erasmus&#43; summer scholarships for higher cycles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/convocatoriaka103verano/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/convocatoriaka103verano/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The students of our higher degree cycles who are interested in doing internships abroad in the summer period of 2021 must apply before May 10, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To do this, they must fill in the application form at the following link:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/docs/docska103/SolicitudKA103.pdf&#34;&gt;https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/docs/docska103/SolicitudKA103.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then they must deliver it to the Erasmus coordinator Daniel Sánchez before that date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the applications have been received, the selection of the participants will be made according to the scale criteria published on our website. The provisional publication of the selected candidates will be made before May 12, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video promotion FP IES Jaroso Erasmus&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/videoerasmus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/videoerasmus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;video autoplay controls&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;source src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2021/video.mp4&#34; type=&#39;video/mp4&#39; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/video&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our colleague Dani has made a wonderful video to promote the Erasmus + project at IES Jaroso for the intermediate and higher degree cycles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final KA120 award</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adjudicacionka120def/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adjudicacionka120def/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are among the few centers in Almería with the Erasmus Accreditation (ka120) approved and selected for the period 2021-2027. The Erasmus accreditation implies a commitment to our European vocation for the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Final resolution Erasmus Accreditation (KA120): &lt;a href=&#34;http://sepie.es/convocatoria/resoluciones.html#25&#34;&gt;http://sepie.es/convocatoria/resoluciones.html#25&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sepie.es/doc/comunicacion/publicaciones/2021/KA120_subvenciones_2020.pdf&#34;&gt;http://sepie.es/doc/comunicacion/publicaciones/2021/KA120_subvenciones_2020.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Award KA120</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adjudicacionka120/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adjudicacionka120/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are! Our dream that the Jaroso Vocational Training offers the possibility of practicing and learning in Europe is closer and closer and for all training cycles. We must thank colleague Lorena for all her work, passion and dedication with the Erasmus IES Jaroso program.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certificate of evaluation of Erasmus &#43; applicant students</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/actabaremacion2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/actabaremacion2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As there is only one student who has applied to participate in Erasmus + this course then he is automatically selected.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening of the deadline to apply for Erasmus&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/aperturaerasmusmar21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/aperturaerasmusmar21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The deadline for applying for Erasmus + mobility grants for internships for students in Higher Degree training cycles is now open (both for completing the FCT and for newly graduated students). There are two Erasmus + KA103 mobility grants offered on this occasion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Students in the 2nd year of our Higher Degree training cycles who are interested in taking the professional module FCT (Workplace Training) in the EU (European Union) in the period between March and June 2021, must apply before the December 22, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our commitment to Erasmus &#43; appears in the newspapers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/diarioalmeria_2-10-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/diarioalmeria_2-10-2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;On September 29 this educational center received confirmation from the Spanish Service for the Internationalization of Education (SEPIE), attached to the Ministry of Universities, that its request for mobility for students and teachers within the framework of Higher Education has been accepted between program countries. Specifically, 9 mobilities have been granted for students of the two vocational training cycles of Higher Level of the center (Design of Web Applications and Guide, Information and Tourist Assistance), in addition to another 2 for teachers, and € 14,900 of awarded funds.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Definitively awarded 9 mobilities for the KA103 project</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adju_oficial_1-10-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adju_oficial_1-10-2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The training cycles at IES Jaroso are in luck, our Erasmus+ project to train, learn and live an international experience is now a reality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;9 mobilities for our vocational training cycles: Web Applications Design, and Guide, Information and Tourist Assistance. In total 27 months to distribute.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We could not be happier.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KA103 project awarded</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adjudicado1-09-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/adjudicado1-09-2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another step in the achievement of the Erasmus + KA103 project for the two higher-level training cycles of the IES Jaroso de Cuevas del Almanzora (Design of Web Applications, and Guide, Information and Tourist Assistance). A strong stimulus to bet on Vocational Training and carry out your work practices in a European country. For the period 2020-2022, 9 mobilities have been granted, one can be yours &amp;hellip; Europe awaits you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provisional admission KA102 y KA103</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/provisional2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/provisional2020/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The IES Jaroso has been accepted into the provisional resolution of the projects requested Erasmus+, both KA102 and KA103.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are very happy, we can say that our adventure begins !!!  Congratulations!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks in particular to our coordinator, Lorena, her enormous work has been rewarded, and Dani and Javier who are also giving everything because Erasmus+ is ahead at IES Jaroso.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From now on, to work to make these projects a success story, a lot of encouragement in the future that comes ahead of us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project videos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/videos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;youtube-privacy-enhanced-shortcode&#34;&gt;YouTube Privacy Enhanced Shortcode&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jQlY5q3OVg8?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;youtube-privacy-enhanced-shortcode-1&#34;&gt;YouTube Privacy Enhanced Shortcode&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dxp5kw5CGFk?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
