<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>noticias on Erasmus&#43; IES Jaroso</title>
    <link>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/categories/noticias/</link>
    <description>Recent content in noticias on Erasmus&#43; IES Jaroso</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/categories/noticias/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our commitment to Erasmus &#43; appears in the newspapers</title>
      <link>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/diarioalmeria_2-10-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/diarioalmeria_2-10-2020/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;On September 29 this educational center received confirmation from the Spanish Service for the Internationalization of Education (SEPIE), attached to the Ministry of Universities, that its request for mobility for students and teachers within the framework of Higher Education has been accepted between program countries. Specifically, 9 mobilities have been granted for students of the two vocational training cycles of Higher Level of the center (Design of Web Applications and Guide, Information and Tourist Assistance), in addition to another 2 for teachers, and € 14,900 of awarded funds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definitively awarded 9 mobilities for the KA103 project</title>
      <link>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/adju_oficial_1-10-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/adju_oficial_1-10-2020/</guid>
      <description>The training cycles at IES Jaroso are in luck, our Erasmus+ project to train, learn and live an international experience is now a reality.
9 mobilities for our vocational training cycles: Web Applications Design, and Guide, Information and Tourist Assistance. In total 27 months to distribute.
We could not be happier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KA103 project awarded</title>
      <link>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/adjudicado1-09-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/adjudicado1-09-2020/</guid>
      <description>Another step in the achievement of the Erasmus + KA103 project for the two higher-level training cycles of the IES Jaroso de Cuevas del Almanzora (Design of Web Applications, and Guide, Information and Tourist Assistance). A strong stimulus to bet on Vocational Training and carry out your work practices in a European country. For the period 2020-2022, 9 mobilities have been granted, one can be yours &amp;hellip; Europe awaits you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provisional admission KA102 y KA103</title>
      <link>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/provisional2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.erasmusiesjaroso.com/en/blog/provisional2020/</guid>
      <description>The IES Jaroso has been accepted into the provisional resolution of the projects requested Erasmus+, both KA102 and KA103.
We are very happy, we can say that our adventure begins !!! Congratulations!!!
Thanks in particular to our coordinator, Lorena, her enormous work has been rewarded, and Dani and Javier who are also giving everything because Erasmus+ is ahead at IES Jaroso.
From now on, to work to make these projects a success story, a lot of encouragement in the future that comes ahead of us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>