<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ka121 on Erasmus&#43; IES Jaroso</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/ka121/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ka121 on Erasmus&#43; IES Jaroso</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/tags/ka121/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adama is already in Italy to begin his Erasmus experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/gm_2024_adama_llegado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/gm_2024_adama_llegado/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to share that Adama has arrived in Rome as an Erasmus+ Laboratory student. He will be undertaking internships at a food laboratory in Arezzo for three months. We hope you learn a lot and have an unforgettable experience in this beautiful city!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students from IES Jaroso Vocational Training School ready to start their Erasmus 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/alumnosgm-erasmus-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/alumnosgm-erasmus-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Four students from IES Jaroso, Adama, Sarafina, María José, and Francina, from Vocational Training cycles in Laboratory, Administrative Management, and Welding, have just left the final Erasmus+ meeting and are already prepared to embark on this exciting Erasmus adventure. Soon, a student from the Higher Degree in Web Application Development will also join them. We wish them the best in this unique experience!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2024/foto1-gm.jpg&#34;&gt;Alumnos Erasmus GM 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel to Germany to tutor a student on site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/tutorizandoalemania-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/tutorizandoalemania-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This academic year 2022-2023 we have had a student doing his internship in Dusseldorf, Germany. This week the professor of the Laboratory training cycle, Jaime Usano, traveled there to tutor our student Nitai on site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This contact of the teacher with the reception centers is essential to establish long-term collaboration ties, improve the stay and training of the students and, ultimately, promote the Erasmus project at IES Jaroso.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We love seeing students working in companies in this way, and tutors so happy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The application period for Erasmus &#43; mobility KA121 is open</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/abiertoplazoka121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/abiertoplazoka121/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The deadline for applying for Erasmus + mobility grants for internships for students of Basic and Middle degree cycles is open (for the completion of the FCT).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 2nd year students of our Basic and Medium degree cycles who are interested in taking their FCT in the European Union in the period between March and June 2022, must apply between December 17, 2021 at 9:00 as of December 22, 2021 at 2:00 p.m. To do this, they must fill in:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk Erasmus KA121</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/charlaerasmuska121/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/charlaerasmuska121/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, December 16, 2021, at 18:00, second year students from Basic FP and Middle Cycles interested in participating in the Erasmus Project will be invited to a face-to-face talk at IES Jaroso (door 35, ask at the Concierge).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This talk will be aimed at those students who wish to do Workplace Training in the European Union. In the event that a student is a minor, they may attend accompanied by their legal guardians.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
